The Saints path to the draft presented
by Cox continued Tuesday as they hosted
Tulane's pro day. Tulane football
players had opportunity to showcase
their skills in front of NFL, CFL, UFL
scouts, team execs, and coaches. They
were able to participate in
measurements, on-field workouts, and
drills. I'm just grateful that I had
[music] an opportunity to come out here
and and work with my guys, you know. I
was excited to see those guys. I think
it was just a great day to get some
work. I think got a lot to clean up on,
but hey, you know, like I said, you're
not getting better, you're getting
worse, so
>> [music]
>> I think I got better today, so The
Saints and the Green Wave have had a
relationship over the years where
they're allowed Tulane to come into the
indoor practice facility, host the pro
day, and practice. [music] It's an
opportunity for the players to get out
on an NFL field and see what it's
actually like [music] being in an NFL
building. One Tulane player who's hoping
to hear his name called during the NFL
draft April 23rd through 26th [music] is
quarterback Jake Radcliff. He led the
Tulane Green Wave in passing and [music]
rushing, the first time a quarterback
has ever led the team in rushing in a
single season. He also broke the
single-season touchdown record with 16.
[music] He was invited to the Hula Bowl
and was able to get out here on the
field today and display some of his
abilities. It's awesome [music] throwing
in there. I feel like I threw the ball
really well today. I feel like, you
know, I've been training for the last
what, 3 months [music] now, and I feel
like it's paid off in a lot of great
ways today.
>> Stay tuned to New Orleans Saints.com as
we continue the path [music] to the
draft April 23rd through 26th in
Pittsburgh.